Guide to the Henry Hale Bucher, Sr. and Louise Scott Bucher Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
Henry Hale Bucher, Sr. and Louise Scott Bucher Papers
1920-2012
RG 249
Yale University Divinity School Library
7
(15 boxes + 1 portfolio)
This collection documents the life and work of the Rev. Henry Hale Bucher, Sr. and his wife Louise Catron Scott Bucher, who served as Presbyterian missionaries in China and the Philippines, and as fraternal workers in Thailand from 1929 to 1972. The bulk of the collection consists of correspondence from the Buchers to their families and their children. Writings of the Buchers, biographical documentation, collected material, photographs, and audio materials document their missionary work as well as their time in the Santo Tomas and Los Ba単os internment camps in the Philippines during World War II, when forced to leave China by the Japanese occupation.
Bucher, Henry Hale, 1907-1998
Bucher, Louise Catron Scott, 1908-1996
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Dr. Henry Hale Bucher, Jr., 2012, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
Chronology
1907 Dec 7 Henry Hale Bucher born in Pennington, New Jersey to the Rev. George Hough Bucher and Anna Williams Hale Bucher
1908 Oct 12 Louise Catron Scott born in Childress, Montgomery County, Virginia to Samuel Alexander Scott and Lucy Alma Lucas Scott
1924-1928 Henry attended and graduated from Westminster College, New Wilmington, Pennsylvania
1926-1933 Louise attended and graduated from State Teachers College, East Radford, Virginia and taught biology at Radford High School
1929-1931 Henry taught at Bangkok Christian College in Bangkok, Siam [Thailand], appointed by Presbyterian Board of Foreign Missions.
1931-1934 Henry attended and graduated from Princeton Theological Seminary
1933 Sep 6 Henry and Louise married in Roanoke, Virginia.
1934 Commissioned by the Presbyterian Board of Foreign Missions to work on the island of Hainan, South China, first stationed in Kiungchow [now Qiongshan], Hainan and later in Nodoa.
1934 Nov 8 Birth of first child, daughter Anna Louise Bucher, in Haikow [Haikou], Hainan
1936 Mar 7 Birth of second child, son Henry H. Bucher, Jr.
1937 Jun 6 Twin daughters born, Priscilla Jo and Dorothy June. Dorothy was stillborn and Priscilla was disabled at birth.
1937 Sep Family moved to Hong Kong, staying at Phillips House, due to health reasons and Sino-Japanese war.
1938 Family returned to Hainan, stationed in Nodoa. Henry worked with Loi people group in island's interior.
1939 Conditions on Hainan deteriorating due to Japanese occupation, the family left for furlough in the U.S. Christmas 1939 was spent in Roanoke, Virginia.
1940 Sep Returned to China on Canadian liner, Empress of Russia. Henry and Louise enrolled in the School for Chinese Learning in Peiping [Beijing] to learn Mandarin.
1941Jan Bucher family evacuated to Philippine Islands, initially staying in Baguio and later Manila. Bucher taught at Union High School and Union Theological Seminary.
1941 Dec Family evacuated to Los Ba単os during bombing of Manila, then returned to Manila.
1942 Jan Bucher interned at University of Santo Tomas while Louise and children remained in occupied Manila but allowed to return after two weeks. Second son, George Scott Bucher, born.
1944 Jul Family relocated from occupied Manila to Los Ba単os internment camp. Food became scarce as internment continued.
1945 Feb U.S. soldiers and Filipinos enabled the escape of internees from enabled escape of internees from Los Ba単os camp; internees housed on New Bilibad prison grounds until repatriation.
1945 May Bucher family returned to U.S. on USS Eberlee and went to New Jersey and later to Hartford, Connecticut where Henry and Louise enrolled at Hartford Seminary.
1946 Dec Family returned to China, stationed at Kiungchow [now Qiongshan], Hainan.
1948-1949 Children Anna and Henry, Jr. attended boarding school at Shanghai American School.
1949 Spring Family went to Hong Kong where Henry, Sr. was hospitalized with amoebic dysentery. Doctor recommended health leave to the U.S. in the summer of 1949
1949 Jul Bucher family returned to U.S. and resided in New Jersey.
1950-1955 Bucher served as Associate Director of Missionary Education in the Presbyterian (U.S.A.) Board of Christian Education, Philadelphia
1956-1972 Henry and Louise Bucher served in Phetburi,Thailand under the Mission Board of the Presbyterian Church U.S.A.
1964 Daughter Priscilla severely burned when her clothes accidentally caught fire in the family's Phetburi kitchen. This added to the trauma of cerebral palsy from childbirth.
1972-1977 The Buchers retired and went to live in Chattanooga, TN where Henry engaged in various temporary pastoral positions at four Presbyterian churches in the area.
1978 For health considerations, the Buchers left Chattanooga for retirement communities, initially in Leesburg, Florida and later in Santa Fe, New Mexico, and at Westminster Garden in Duarte, California. While in Leesburg, Henry was the organizing pastor of the Lake Square Presbyterian Church.
1996 Nov 8 Louise Bucher died. In 1997 her ashes were buried half near Roanoke, Virginia, and half in Phetburi, Thailand.
1998 Nov 25 Henry H. Bucher, Sr. died. In 1999 his ashes were buried half near Roanoke, Virginia, and half in Phetburi Thailand
Scope and Contents
This collection provides valuable insight into the life and work of Presbyterian missionaries Henry Hale Bucher, Sr. and Louise Scott Bucher. The Buchers were involved in missionary work from 1929 to 1972 and served in a variety of settings, from Henry Bucher's initial period of teaching at Bangkok Christian College through their years stationed in Hainan, South China, evacuation to the Philippines during World War II, time spent in internment camps, a return to China after the war, evacuation due to the Communist takeover in China, and eventual return to mission work in Thailand.
Series I, Family Correspondence, contains frequent, detailed letters that the Buchers wrote home to their families. These letters provide excellent documentation of their mission activities, family life, and the political disruptions of the time. The letters of Henry tend to be more substantial in terms of describing events, issues, and activities of their work, while Louise's letters deal more with family matters. The series includes both "circular" type letters addressed to the home families in general as well as letters addressed to specific family members. Letters written by Henry and Louise to their own children in later years, are more personal in nature and less descriptive of mission activities.
Most valuable in Series II, General Correspondence, are the circular letters that the Buchers sent to their supporters and friends at home. These provide a succinct overview of their work in the various venues where they found themselves. Also of interest in this series are letters written to the Buchers by former students and colleagues in China and Thailand, as well as communications from Board of Foreign Missions of the Presbyterian Church and from the American Consulate regarding the situation for missionaries in China and Philippines during war.
Series III, Writings and Notes of the Buchers, includes interesting journal-type writings by Henry that describe his mission trips into the countryside in great detail. Also contained in this series are writings from the period when Henry was Associate Director of Missionary Education in the Presbyterian (U.S.A.) Board of Christian Education. Extensive sermon notes from through Henry's life are also included.
Series IV, Collected Material, is organized according to the various stages of their work. Documentation of the Hainan Mission of the Presbyterian Church U.S.A. is particularly rich. Also of significant interest is collected material relating to the internment camps in the Philippines during the Second World War and in particular the raid by the U.S. Army that rescued inhabitants of the Los Ba単os camp.
Series V, Personal Items and Memorabilia, is divided into three sections: Biographical documentation, Artifacts and certificates, and Audio-visual materials. This series fills out the story of the Buchers' internment experience both through biographical documentation and through audio-visual materials. Numerous photographs trace the growth of the Bucher family and illustrate the venues where they worked.
Arrangement
I. Family Correspondence
II. General Correspondence
III. Writings and Notes of the Buchers
IV. Collected Materials
V. Personal Items and Memorabilia
Missions -- China; Missions -- Thailand; World War, 1939-1945 -- Prisoners and prisons, Japanese; Bucher, Henry Hale, 1907-1998; Bucher, Louise Catron Scott, 1908-1996; Presbyterian Church in the U.S.A -- Missions -- China
- Family Correspondence, Series I
  - To families of Henry Hale Bucher Sr. and Louise Catron Scott Bucher
    Scope and Contents
    This subseries contains letters addressed to "Dear Families" or "Dearest Families" - typescript letters generally addressed to the families of Henry and Louise. Letters addressed to specific family members are contained in the following two subseries.
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow [Qiongzhou], Hainan, including regarding birth of daughter Anna Louise, language study, new home, 1934 Oct - 1935 Mar (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding a church service and election of Elders, and birth of son Henry, 1935 Aug - 1936 Dec (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including mission work, growth of children Anna Louise, Henry, and new baby Priscilla (surviving twin), 1937 Apr - 1937 Oct (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Nodoa, including regarding Henry's trip to the Loi country, interactions with fellow missionaries, 1938 Feb - 1939 Jan (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 12 letters, witten by Henry and Louise from Nodoa, College of Chinese Studies (Peking) and Philippines, including regarding disruptions of war, 1939 Feb - 1941 Apr (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 9 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Manila, 1941 Jun - Sep (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 12 letters, written by Henry and Louise following internment, from boat and Hongkong, return to Kiungchow, Hainan in February 1947, 1946 Dec - 1947 Dec (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 9 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding Henry's trip to Ngai Tsui, mission work, 1948 Jan - 1948 May (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding "Christianizing the Home" campaign, economic situation, 1948 May - 1948 Nov (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding Anna Louise and Henry, Jr. at Shanghai American School, Henry's trips to countryside, 1948 Nov - 1949 Apr (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, Hong Kong, New Jersey, Thailand, Florida, 1949 Apr - 1981, no date (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - To/from family of Louise Scott Bucher
    - 10 letters, primarily written by Louise from Kiungchow, Hainan, South China, regarding family matters, 1934 Aug - 1935 Dec (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding birth of son, 1936 Feb - 1937 Feb (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 8 letters, written by Louise from Kiungchow, Hong Kong, and Nodoa, Hainan, including regarding expecting twins, 1937 Mar - 1938 Mar (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Nodoa; letters from Henry describe trip into Loi country, Easter services, summer Bible School, 1938 Apr - 1939 Feb (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise while on furlough in U.S., 1939 Nov - 1940, no date circa 1930s (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 7 letters, written by Louise from Beijing and beginning in March 1941 from the Philippines, 1940 Oct - 1941 Nov (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 13 letters, including letter to Scott family from Marjorie Judson, missionary colleague of the Buchers, regarding events in Philippines; letters from Louise, Henry, and children on American Red Cross stationery, following internment, and from ship returning to U.S., 1944 Feb - 1945 Apr (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 9 letters, written by Louise and Henry after return to Hainan, including regarding trip by Henry to Zi-lim, Ngai Tsiu, Hainanese marital and religious customs, 1947 Feb - 1949 Jun (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 4 letters, written by Louise and Henry enroute to Thailand and from Bangkok and Phetchaburi [Phet Buri; referred to by Buchers as Phetburi or Petburi), 1956 Oct - 1959 May (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 10 letters, from Louise and Henry in Phetburi and from Miss Yupa Oonyawongse, who had visited relatives of Louise in the U.S., 1962 Jan - 1963 Dec (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, Thailand, including regarding accident that left daughter Priscilla with severe burns, 1964 Jan - 1964 Oct 3 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 9 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1964 Oct 6 - 1964 Nov (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 12 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1964 Nov - 1965 Jan (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 8 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi and Bangkok, 1965 Feb - Apr 6 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise Henry, and Priscilla from Phetburi, 1965 Apr 10 - 1965 Aug 4 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise, Henry and Priscilla from Phetburi, 1965 Aug 21 - 1966 Jan (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 11 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1966 Feb - 1966 Jul (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 9 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1966 Jul - 1967 Mar 9 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 11 letters, written by Louise and Henry, from Bangkok and Phetburi, 1967 Mar 6 - 1967 Nov (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1968 Jan - Jul (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 6 letters, written by Louise from Phetburi, 1968 Aug, circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise from Phetburi and Bangkok, 1970 Feb - 1970 Jul (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise from Phetburi, 1970 Aug - Nov (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1970 Dec - 1971 May (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1971 Jun - 1972 Jan (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi, 1972 Mar - -1974 Aug (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 13 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Phetburi and Bangkok, 1975 Jan, circa 1970s (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Leesburg, Florida, 1981 Oct - 1983 Nov (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Leesburg, Florida, 1984 Jan - 1984 Jun (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 10 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Leesburg, Florida, 1984 Jun - 1984 Oct (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 7 letters, written by Louise and Henry from Leesburg, Florida, 1984 Dec - 1987 Jun (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 4 undated letters from Louise to family; 2 letters from Aunt Clara, 1965, 1967, no date (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous letters written by Clara Scott and other family members to the Buchers, 1960s-1970s (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - To/from family of Henry Hale Bucher, Sr.
    - 11 letters, written by Henry regarding trip to Pak Saa, Thailand and teaching at Bangkok Christian College (1930-1931); from Roanoke, VA and en route to China with Louise (1934), 1930 Feb - 1934 Jul (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise regarding arrival in Hongkong and station at Kiungchow, Hainan, 1934 Aug - 1934 Nov (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Hainan, including regarding birth of daughter Anna Louise and Chinese life and customs, kite flying, 1934 Nov - 1935 Feb (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding Chinese New Year rites, language study, beliefs of fellow missionaries, 1935 Feb - 1935 Apr (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise regarding Henry's trip to countryside of Hainan and contact with Loi tribe, from visit to Hongkong, and return to Kiungchow, 1935 May - 1935 Aug (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Hainan, including regarding Sunday School and Bible classes, 1935 Sep - 1935 Dec (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, 1936 Jan - 1936 Feb (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding birth of son Henry, 1936 Mar - 1936 Sep (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 14 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow and Hoihow including regard Henry's trips to visit churches in the countryside, Chinese religious festivals, 1936 Sep - 1937 May (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 20 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, including regarding birth of twin daughters, of whom Priscilla Jo survived, language study, Henry's trips to countryside, trip to Hong Kong, return to Nodoa, Hainan, baptism of Chinese Christians, 1937 Jun - 1938 Apr (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 9 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Nodoa, including regarding ordination of Chinese clergy, 1938 May - 1938 Nov (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Nodoa and then on furlough in Roanoke, VA and Princeton, NJ, 1938 Dec - 1940 Sep (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise enroute to China, from College of Chinese Studies, Peiping [Beijing], including regarding plans for evacuation to Philippines, 1940 Sep - 1941 Jan (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise enroute to Philippines, from Baguio, from Manila, 1941 Feb - 1941 Jul (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 14 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Manila (1941-1942) and from "somewhere in the Philippines" following internment (1945); 1 letter to George H. Bucher from U.S. Department of the Interior regarding internment of Bucher family by Japanese; 1 letter to Bucher relatives from Presbyterian Board of Missions announcing repatriation of Bucher family; 1 letter from brother-in-law Fred Fowler regarding Bucher family upon repatriation, 1941 Aug, 1942 Feb, 1945 Mar, May (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 12 letters, written by Henry and Louise, from Hong Kong, from Kiungchow, Hainan; one letter to George H. Bucher from Presbyterian Board of Missions reassuring him of his son's safety, 1947 Jan - Nov (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 12 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, 1948 Jan - Jul (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - 7 letters, written by Henry and Louise, from Hong Kong, including regarding Anna Louise and Henry going to school at Shanghai American School, 1948 Aug - Dec (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - 8 letters, written by Henry and Louise from Kiungchow, 1949, no date (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise, from Roanoke and Thailand, 1957, 1964, no date (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 13 letters to Henry and Louise primarily from Robert and Carol Bucher, 1947 Aug - 1964 Feb, no date (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 10 letters to Henry and Louise primarily from Robert and Carol Bucher, 1964 Mar - 1965 Mar (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - 9 letters to Henry and Louise from Robert and Carol Bucher and G. Hale Bucher, 1965 Apr - 1995 Nov (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - 3 letters to Henry and Louise with note from George Bucher while in Manila, P.I., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - To/from Bucher children and Louise
    - Various
      - 20 letters and cards to parents,grandparents from children of Henry and Louise, 1945-1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Serial letter written by Henry to Louise and children while on itinerating trip to Hai Bak Peninsula, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - 10 letters, written by Henry to children and Louise, primarily from trip to Zi-lim, Ngai Tsui (many with typed transcripts), 1947 Aug - Dec (Box 2, Folder 26a)
      - 5 letters, written by Henry to children and Louise during trips to the interior, including Si-vun area (with typed transcripts), 1948 May, Nov; 1949 Jan-Feb (Box 2, Folder 26b)
        See also "Dear Diary" letters from same time period in Series IV, Writings
      - 10 letters, written by Henry and Louise to children, en route to Thailand, 1956 - 1958 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - 15 letters, written by Henry and Louise to children from Thailand, 1959 - 1963 (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - 8 letters, written by Henry and Louise to children from Thailand, 1964 - 1967 (Box 2, Folder 29)
      - Miscellaneous letters to/from children and other family members, including Scott to Aunt Clara Scott and regarding deteriorating health of Louise in later years, 1966, 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Miscellaneous letters to/from children, spouses, and other family members, 1994 - 1995, no date (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Priscilla Bucher
      - Letters to parents while she was in Montana and they were in Thailand, 1962-1964 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Letters to parents while she was in Wisconsin and her parents were in Thailand, including two letters from the woman with whom she was residing., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Henry H. Bucher, Jr.
      - 15 letters and card from parents in New Jersey, en route to Thailand, 1955 Oct - 1956 Oct (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - 8 letters from parents en route to Thailand, from Bangkok, 1956 Nov (Box 2, Folder 33)
      - 11 letters from parents in Bangkok, 1956 Dec (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - 12 letters from parents and Priscilla in Bangkok, 1957 Jan (Box 2, Folder 35)
      - 10 letters from parents and Priscilla in Bangkok, 1957 Feb (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - 11 letters from parents and Priscilla in Bangkok, 1957 Mar (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - 3 letters from parents in Thailand, 1957 Apr (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - 14 letters from parents and Priscilla in Bangkok, 1957 May - Jun (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 23 letters from parents and Priscilla in Bangkok and Phetburi [Phetchaburi], 1958 Feb - Sep (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - 12 letters from parents in Bangkok and Phetburi, 1958 Oct - 1958 Nov (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - 11 letters from parents in Phetburi and Bangkok, 1958 Dec - 1959 Jan (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - 26 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1959 Feb - Jun (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi and Bangkok, 1959 Jun - Nov (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1959 Nov - 1960 May (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1960 May - 1962 Dec (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1962 Dec - 1963 Aug (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1963 Sep - 1964 Feb (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi and Roanoke, 1964 Feb - Jul (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - 30 letters from parents in U.S. and Phetburi; one letter from Nick Lash in Phetburi, 1964 Jul - 1965 Mar (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - 29 letters from parents and Priscilla in Phetburi, 1965 Mar - 1966 Sep (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1966 Sep - 1967 Mar (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1967 Mar - Oct (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - 30 letters from parents in Phetburi, 1967 Oct - 1968 Apr (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - 20 letters from parents in Phetburi and U.S., 1968 Aug - 1997, no dates (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Louise and Henry Sr. to/from each other
    - 13 letters to/from Louise and Henry, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- General Correspondence, Series II
  - Circular letters from Buchers to supporters and friends
    - 9 letters, Henry from Bangkok Christian College (1931); Henry and Louise from Kiungchow and Nodoa, 1931, 1934, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)